

### **PROFILE**

Anupam Shringi is a senior manager within center of data & insights team of Accenture Applied Intelligence and has 13+ years of experience in championing data strategy, data driven insights and developing offerings using client and multiple external data sources.

He has helped sell and deliver high profile digital transformation projects across the globe spanning multiple industries. He also has significant international exposure including a 3-year stint at Accenture Hong Kong.

### CONTACT

PHONE: +91-9611997500

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anupamshringi-93a2785/

FMAII.

ashringi@gmail.com

## **SKILLS**



# ANUPAM SHRINGI

SENIOR ANALYTICS CONSULTING MANAGER

## **WORK EXPERIENCE (KEY HIGHLIGHTS)**

**ACCENTURE, Senior Analytics Consulting Manager** New Delhi, Hong Kong, San Francisco, Bangalore May 2010 - Present

- Led the data strategy and creation of digital prospect 360
  using for US digital only bank multiple third-party data sources
  to innovatively personalize and prioritize personal loan
  targeting resulting in 60% decrease in cost per acquisition
- Led a team of consultants in a pilot project for a Hong Kong banking client and over a period of 2.5 months delivered a three times response rate over the existing campaign using analytics driven marketing strategy. This led to a multi-year deal with the client.
- Supported and converted multiple proposals and business development activities with Accenture MDs and interacted with CMOs and CIOs of large financial organizations to understand business problems and developed solutions.
- Delivered valuable marketing insights by analyzing billions of credit card transactions per day using big data technologies such as Hadoop, Hive, etc. for a large US payment gateway provider in USA. Helped the client in integrating the data from various sources such as web, airlines, hotel booking data
- Delivered data strategy roadmap & analytics driven
   Campaign design for large insurance client using machine learning models to identify the customers who are most likely to buy certain insurance products.

#### Capillary Technologies, Customer success Manager

Hong Kong & Bangalore Sep 2015 to Mar 2016

> Capture real time customer POS data and manage loyalty programs and analytics for leading Hong Kong and Indian Apparel brands

#### **EDUCATION**

# Indian Institute of Technology Kharagpur

2004-2008

Civil engineering major from one of the leading technical universities in India. Won multiple music society and fest competitions